1
00:04:42,432 --> 00:04:44,593
- Good night, Pat.
- Good night.

2
00:04:47,737 --> 00:04:52,197
- What happened? Old bank was beautiful.
- People kept robbing it.

3
00:04:52,275 --> 00:04:54,800
It's a small price to pay for beauty.

4
00:05:00,883 --> 00:05:02,976
Hit me.

5
00:05:06,422 --> 00:05:08,253
Again.

6
00:05:10,693 --> 00:05:12,217
Bust!

7
00:05:14,664 --> 00:05:16,655
Give me credit, Mr Macon?

8
00:05:16,766 --> 00:05:18,825
You know my rules, Tom.

9
00:05:20,470 --> 00:05:23,803
Well, looks like you just about
cleaned everybody out, fella.

10
00:05:23,873 --> 00:05:26,774
You haven't lost a hand
since you got the deal.

11
00:05:27,510 --> 00:05:30,001
What's the secret of your success?

12
00:05:33,082 --> 00:05:35,175
Prayer.

13
00:05:35,685 --> 00:05:37,778
Let's just you and me play.

14
00:05:54,837 --> 00:05:56,896
Hit it.

15
00:06:00,643 --> 00:06:02,702
Bust!

16
00:06:05,114 --> 00:06:07,912
Yeah. You're a hell of a card player, fella.

17
00:06:08,684 --> 00:06:11,346
I know, cos I'm a hell of a card player.

18
00:06:12,889 --> 00:06:15,824
And I can't even spot how you're cheating.

19
00:06:29,338 --> 00:06:31,670
The money stays and you go.

20
00:06:35,278 --> 00:06:39,442
Well, we seem to be a little short
on brotherly love around here.

21
00:06:39,515 --> 00:06:43,281
- If you're with him,
you better get out of here.
- We're on our way.

22
00:06:43,886 --> 00:06:45,444
- Come on.
- I wasn't cheating.

23
00:06:45,521 --> 00:06:46,852
- Come on!
- I wasn't!

24
00:06:46,923 --> 00:06:50,984
You can die.
For that matter, you can both die.

25
00:06:51,094 --> 00:06:53,528
- Hear that?
- If he invites us to stay, we'll go.

26
00:06:53,663 --> 00:06:57,929
- We were gonna leave anyway.
- He's gotta invite us to stick around.

27
00:06:59,102 --> 00:07:02,902
He'll draw on you. He's ready.
You don't know how fast he is.

28
00:07:11,114 --> 00:07:15,414
- I'm over the hill, but it can happen to you.
- That's just what I wanna hear.

29
00:07:15,518 --> 00:07:18,419
Every day you get older. Now, that's a law.

30
00:07:29,365 --> 00:07:32,596
What would you think about
maybe asking us to stick around?

31
00:07:32,735 --> 00:07:35,033
- What?
- You don't have to mean it.

32
00:07:35,138 --> 00:07:38,005
Just ask us to stick around. I promise you...

33
00:07:45,848 --> 00:07:48,146
I can't help you, Sundance.

34
00:07:58,761 --> 00:08:03,323
I didn't know you were the Sundance Kid
when I said you were cheating.

35
00:08:06,269 --> 00:08:09,397
If I draw on you, you'll kill me.

36
00:08:09,472 --> 00:08:12,134
There's that possibility.

37
00:08:12,208 --> 00:08:16,872
No. You'd be killing yourself. So why
don't you just invite us to stick around?

38
00:08:19,382 --> 00:08:21,350
Now, you can do it.

39
00:08:21,417 --> 00:08:23,749
And easy. Come on.

40
00:08:26,155 --> 00:08:28,214
Come on.

41
00:08:30,693 --> 00:08:32,684
Why don't you stick around?

42
00:08:32,828 --> 00:08:35,490
Thanks, but we gotta get going.

43
00:08:42,038 --> 00:08:43,835
Hey, Kid.

44
00:08:43,906 --> 00:08:46,204
Hey, Kid! How good are ya?

45
00:08:57,587 --> 00:09:00,283
Like I been telling you, over the hill.

46
00:09:57,747 --> 00:10:03,276
Boy, every time I see Hole in the Wall again,
it's like seeing it fresh for the first time.

47
00:10:03,352 --> 00:10:07,311
And every time that happens
I keep asking myself the same question.

48
00:10:07,390 --> 00:10:10,951
How can I be so damn stupid
as to keep coming back here?

49
00:10:16,332 --> 00:10:19,267
- What's your idea this time?
- Bolivia.

50
00:10:21,737 --> 00:10:25,798
- What's Bolivia?
- Bolivia. That's a country, stupid.

51
00:10:25,941 --> 00:10:28,933
In Central or South America. One or the other.

52
00:10:30,079 --> 00:10:32,274
Why don't we just go to Mexico instead?

53
00:10:32,348 --> 00:10:36,011
Cos all they got in Mexico is sweat.
There's too much of that here.

54
00:10:36,118 --> 00:10:39,747
If we'd been in business in the California
gold rush, where'd we have gone?

55
00:10:39,822 --> 00:10:41,517
- California, right?
- Right.

56
00:10:41,590 --> 00:10:44,616
So when I say Bolivia,
you just think California.

57
00:10:47,330 --> 00:10:51,790
You wouldn't believe what they're
finding in the ground down there.

58
00:10:51,901 --> 00:10:54,495
Silver mines, gold mines, tin mines.

59
00:10:54,570 --> 00:10:58,199
Payrolls so heavy
we'd strain ourselves stealing them.

60
00:11:00,443 --> 00:11:04,209
You just keep thinking, Butch.
That's what you're good at!

61
00:11:04,313 --> 00:11:08,215
Boy, I got vision and
the rest of the world wears bifocals.

62
00:11:30,406 --> 00:11:32,567
Hi, News. Whatcha doing?

63
00:11:32,641 --> 00:11:35,838
Oh, howdy, Butch. Nothing.

64
00:11:35,945 --> 00:11:37,640
Nothing.

65
00:11:37,747 --> 00:11:39,214
Howdy, Sundance.

66
00:11:39,415 --> 00:11:42,680
Well, you sure are.
You're doing something. What?

67
00:11:46,188 --> 00:11:50,420
Just fixing to rob the Union Pacific Flyer,
Butch. That's all we had in mind.

68
00:11:51,894 --> 00:11:54,863
You fellas got everything I told you all wrong.

69
00:11:55,097 --> 00:11:57,657
True, we might hit the Flyer,

70
00:11:57,767 --> 00:12:01,635
but even if we do, it won't be this run.
It'll be the next one - the return.

71
00:12:01,704 --> 00:12:05,504
- Sundance and me been checking the banks.
- No banks.

72
00:12:05,608 --> 00:12:07,473
What?

73
00:12:08,277 --> 00:12:10,768
The Flyer, Butch.

74
00:12:11,981 --> 00:12:15,178
Fellas, bad as they are,
banks are better than trains.

75
00:12:15,251 --> 00:12:19,017
They don't move. They stay put.
You know the money's in there.

76
00:12:19,121 --> 00:12:22,488
- When I left I gave orders.
- New orders been given.

77
00:12:22,591 --> 00:12:24,650
Well, I run things here, Harvey.

78
00:12:25,327 --> 00:12:27,386
Used to you did.

79
00:12:27,463 --> 00:12:29,522
Me now.

80
00:12:30,666 --> 00:12:32,725
This don't concern you!

81
00:12:35,037 --> 00:12:38,939
- You tell him to stay out.
- Well, he goes his own way like always.

82
00:12:40,409 --> 00:12:43,037
What's the matter with you guys?

83
00:12:43,112 --> 00:12:45,808
When I came here, you weren't even a gang.
I formed ya!

84
00:12:45,881 --> 00:12:48,406
- Who says?
- Well, read them a clipping, News.

85
00:12:48,484 --> 00:12:50,748
- Which one?
- Any of them!

86
00:12:55,691 --> 00:12:58,751
This one here's from the Salt Lake Herald.

87
00:12:58,861 --> 00:13:04,663
- "Butch Cassidy's Hole in the Wall Gang..."
- Butch Cassidy's gang - that's me!

88
00:13:04,733 --> 00:13:08,829
You want Harvey to do your planning?
To do your thinking? To run things?

89
00:13:08,904 --> 00:13:11,668
- "...outlaws with them on..."
- Shut up now, News!

90
00:13:11,740 --> 00:13:13,867
Not till I get to the good part, Butch.

91
00:13:13,943 --> 00:13:19,347
"Known to have participated in the holdup
are Flat Nose Curry and News Carver."

92
00:13:19,448 --> 00:13:23,043
I just love to read my name in the paper,
Butch.

93
00:13:23,118 --> 00:13:26,087
OK, so we forget about Logan taking over.
OK, Flat Nose?

94
00:13:26,155 --> 00:13:28,783
You always said any one of us
could challenge you.

95
00:13:28,891 --> 00:13:33,726
- It's cos I figured no one would do it.
- Figured wrong, Butch.

96
00:13:34,396 --> 00:13:36,887
You guys can't want Logan!

97
00:13:37,967 --> 00:13:41,960
At least he's with us, Butch.
You've been spending a lot of time gone.

98
00:13:42,071 --> 00:13:44,539
- Cos everything's different.
- Guns or knives?

99
00:13:44,607 --> 00:13:49,544
- It's harder now. You gotta plan more.
- Guns or knives?!

100
00:13:50,513 --> 00:13:52,208
- Neither.
- Pick!

101
00:13:52,348 --> 00:13:54,816
I don't wanna shoot with you, Harvey.

102
00:13:55,918 --> 00:13:58,182
Anything you say, Butch.

103
00:14:14,169 --> 00:14:17,104
Maybe there's a way to make a profit in this.

104
00:14:18,440 --> 00:14:20,635
Bet on Logan.

105
00:14:20,743 --> 00:14:23,906
- I would, but who'd bet on you?
- Sundance,

106
00:14:25,347 --> 00:14:30,114
when we're done, if he's dead,
you're welcome to stay.

107
00:14:31,153 --> 00:14:36,352
Listen, I don't mean to be a sore loser,
but when it's done, if I'm dead, kill him.

108
00:14:36,425 --> 00:14:38,518
Love to.

109
00:14:48,070 --> 00:14:52,063
No, no, not yet. Not until me and Harvey
get the rules straightened out.

110
00:14:52,174 --> 00:14:55,075
Rules? In a knife fight? No rules!

111
00:14:56,812 --> 00:15:00,179
If there ain't no rules, let's start.
Someone count 1, 2, 3, go.

112
00:15:00,249 --> 00:15:02,342
1, 2, 3, go!

113
00:15:05,254 --> 00:15:07,984
I was really rooting for you, Butch.

114
00:15:08,057 --> 00:15:10,025
Well, thank you, Flat Nose.

115
00:15:10,859 --> 00:15:13,987
That's what sustained me
in my time of trouble.

116
00:15:15,664 --> 00:15:18,224
Hey, what's this about the Flyer?

117
00:15:18,300 --> 00:15:21,064
Harvey said we'd hit it
both this run and the return.

118
00:15:21,170 --> 00:15:25,300
Nobody's done that to the Flyer before.
No matter how much we got the first time,

119
00:15:25,441 --> 00:15:29,571
they'd figure the return was safe
and load it up with money.

120
00:15:29,645 --> 00:15:32,580
- Harvey thought of that?!
- Yes, sir. He did.

121
00:15:33,916 --> 00:15:37,477
Well, I'll tell you something.
That's exactly what we're gonna do.

122
00:16:14,923 --> 00:16:17,221
- Stop it!
- Where?

123
00:16:17,760 --> 00:16:19,728
Up ahead there.

124
00:16:20,229 --> 00:16:22,925
Bet that's old Butch himself!

125
00:16:29,738 --> 00:16:31,831
Hold it there.

126
00:16:32,474 --> 00:16:36,433
- I just thought I'd watch.
- Bring the kids, why don't you?

127
00:16:36,545 --> 00:16:38,638
Stick your heads in.

128
00:16:39,181 --> 00:16:42,173
You'll get yourself blown up,
you don't open that door.

129
00:16:42,284 --> 00:16:47,051
I can't do that on account of I work for
EH Harriman of the Union Pacific Railroad...

130
00:16:47,122 --> 00:16:50,091
Shut up about that EH Harriman stuff
and open the door!

131
00:16:50,159 --> 00:16:52,753
- What's going on?
- We got a patriot in there.

132
00:16:52,861 --> 00:16:56,854
- OK, go ahead, News.
- That's Woodcock. He's awful dedicated.

133
00:16:56,932 --> 00:16:58,991
- Woodcock!
- Yes, sir.

134
00:17:00,102 --> 00:17:01,694
You know who we are?

135
00:17:01,770 --> 00:17:05,103
You're the Hole in the Wall Gang,
Mr Cassidy. I understand.

136
00:17:05,174 --> 00:17:09,611
But you gotta understand Mr EH Harriman
himself of the Union Pacific give me this job.

137
00:17:09,712 --> 00:17:14,809
- I've gotta do my best, don't you see?
- That don't include getting yourself killed!

138
00:17:14,917 --> 00:17:18,216
- Dynamite's ready.
- Mr EH Harriman had the confidence...

139
00:17:18,320 --> 00:17:24,088
Open the door or that's it! Do you think EH
Harriman would get himself killed for you?

140
00:17:24,159 --> 00:17:25,786
Woodcock?

141
00:17:25,894 --> 00:17:31,196
I work for Mr EH Harriman of the Union
Pacific Railroad, and he entrusted me...

142
00:17:47,516 --> 00:17:50,349
Hey, Woodcock.
Hey, Woodcock, you all right?

143
00:17:50,419 --> 00:17:52,216
Hey.

144
00:17:58,594 --> 00:18:01,620
Whatever Harriman's paying you ain't enough.

145
00:18:10,272 --> 00:18:13,537
There ain't what I'd call a fortune in there,
Butch.

146
00:18:13,609 --> 00:18:17,170
Well, just so we come out ahead.
That's the main thing.

147
00:18:18,547 --> 00:18:23,416
The Hole in the Wall Gang, I guess you heard,
robbed the Flyer outside our town,

148
00:18:23,485 --> 00:18:28,479
so that makes it our responsibility
to get out there and get after them.

149
00:18:28,590 --> 00:18:31,650
Now,
you're gonna have to bring your own horses.

150
00:18:31,794 --> 00:18:34,388
How many of you can bring your own guns?

151
00:18:38,000 --> 00:18:42,767
Yeah, well, how many of you are going
to want me to supply you with guns?

152
00:18:46,508 --> 00:18:51,070
Well... Come on, now. I think it's
up to us to do something, don't you?

153
00:18:51,180 --> 00:18:54,411
Why? They're probably halfway
to Hole in the Wall already.

154
00:18:54,483 --> 00:18:57,611
That's just exactly why we have got to hurry.

155
00:18:57,686 --> 00:19:01,884
If we get mounted up right now and
get after them, maybe we could head them off.

156
00:19:01,990 --> 00:19:05,050
Head them off? You crazy?
We did that, they'd kill us.

157
00:19:05,127 --> 00:19:09,860
Well, I don't think we want to lie down
and just let them get away with this...

158
00:19:12,034 --> 00:19:14,502
Boy, I just eat this up with a spoon!

159
00:19:15,237 --> 00:19:18,206
All right, you two. I want you at my party.

160
00:19:18,273 --> 00:19:21,401
- What party?
- I'm losing my piano player.

161
00:19:21,476 --> 00:19:23,706
He's going off to fight the war.

162
00:19:23,846 --> 00:19:26,280
- What war?
- The war with the Spanish.

163
00:19:26,348 --> 00:19:28,441
"Remember the Maine."

164
00:19:29,318 --> 00:19:33,550
- Who can forget it?
- I'm giving him a send-off, so come on.

165
00:19:42,164 --> 00:19:47,329
Goodbye, Dolly, I must leave you...

166
00:19:47,436 --> 00:19:51,167
When I was a kid, I always thought
I was gonna grow up to be a hero.

167
00:19:51,340 --> 00:19:56,277
- Well, it's too late now.
- What'd you say that for?
You didn't have to.

168
00:19:56,345 --> 00:19:59,542
You want me to go, I'll go all alone

169
00:19:59,648 --> 00:20:03,914
and fight the Hole in the Wall Gang.
Hell, that's fine with me.

170
00:20:03,986 --> 00:20:08,582
And you want your kids to know that
you let me do that, that's fine with me!

171
00:20:08,924 --> 00:20:11,392
But I don't think that's what you want.

172
00:20:13,161 --> 00:20:15,595
Is it?

173
00:20:19,134 --> 00:20:22,262
Why don't we enlist? Go fight the Spanish.

174
00:20:22,337 --> 00:20:24,532
You and me in the war.

175
00:20:24,606 --> 00:20:28,975
We got a lot of things going for us.
Experience, maturity, leadership.

176
00:20:29,077 --> 00:20:31,204
I bet we end up officers.

177
00:20:31,313 --> 00:20:33,372
I'd be Major Parker.

178
00:20:34,683 --> 00:20:36,674
Parker?

179
00:20:36,752 --> 00:20:38,811
Yeah, that's my real name.

180
00:20:40,555 --> 00:20:43,149
- Robert LeRoy Parker.
- No fooling?

181
00:20:43,825 --> 00:20:45,952
Yeah.

182
00:20:49,364 --> 00:20:51,764
- Mine's Longbaugh.
- No fooling?

183
00:20:52,701 --> 00:20:56,296
- Long what?
- Harry Longbaugh.

184
00:20:56,371 --> 00:20:59,101
So you'd be Major Longbaugh.
Whaddaya say?

185
00:21:04,146 --> 00:21:07,513
You just keep thinking, Butch.
That's what you're good at!

186
00:21:08,183 --> 00:21:14,418
But you're not frantic! No, sir! You have got
respect for me and I have got respect for you!

187
00:21:14,523 --> 00:21:19,017
That is why I'm your marshal! And that is
why you and you and you are riding with me!

188
00:21:19,127 --> 00:21:21,425
Am I right?

189
00:21:21,730 --> 00:21:24,062
Well? Whaddaya say?

190
00:21:24,599 --> 00:21:26,760
I say this:

191
00:21:26,835 --> 00:21:30,931
I say, ladies and gentlemen,

192
00:21:31,039 --> 00:21:33,803
boys and girls, friends and enemies,

193
00:21:33,875 --> 00:21:36,571
- meet the future!
- The future what?

194
00:21:36,645 --> 00:21:39,739
The future mode of transportation
for this western world.

195
00:21:40,082 --> 00:21:44,143
Now, I'm not gonna make a lot of
extravagant claims for this little machine.

196
00:21:44,219 --> 00:21:48,246
Sure, it'll change your whole life
for the better, but that's all!

197
00:21:48,357 --> 00:21:50,416
What do you think you're doing?

198
00:21:50,492 --> 00:21:53,950
You got the crowd together.
Just thought I'd do a little selling.

199
00:21:54,062 --> 00:21:57,759
- I'm trying to raise a posse here!
- Got a short presentation.

200
00:21:57,833 --> 00:22:01,166
The horse is dead!
You'll see this item sells itself.

201
00:22:01,236 --> 00:22:04,467
Are you going to listen to him,
or come with me?

202
00:22:04,573 --> 00:22:07,906
Butch, Fanny says for you
to come in to her party, right now.

203
00:22:08,010 --> 00:22:14,040
Cheaper than a horse to keep.
No oats, no mess, no kicks, no running away...

204
00:22:14,182 --> 00:22:16,013
Well,

205
00:22:16,885 --> 00:22:21,117
I think I'll get saddled up
and go looking for a woman.

206
00:22:22,391 --> 00:22:24,450
Good hunting.

207
00:22:25,727 --> 00:22:28,423
Shouldn't take more than a couple of days.

208
00:22:33,001 --> 00:22:35,060
I'm not picky.

209
00:22:35,670 --> 00:22:38,798
As long as she's smart, pretty...

210
00:22:39,875 --> 00:22:41,934
and sweet.

211
00:22:42,544 --> 00:22:45,843
And gentle and... tender and...

212
00:22:46,815 --> 00:22:48,942
refined and

213
00:22:49,051 --> 00:22:52,248
lovely and... carefree...

214
00:24:00,755 --> 00:24:02,723
Keep going, teacher lady.

215
00:24:10,398 --> 00:24:12,958
It's OK. Don't mind me. Keep on going.

216
00:24:40,629 --> 00:24:42,722
Let down your hair.

217
00:24:54,276 --> 00:24:56,801
Shake your head.

218
00:26:05,413 --> 00:26:07,347
- Know what I wish?
- What?

219
00:26:07,482 --> 00:26:09,950
That once you'd get here on time!

220
00:26:13,655 --> 00:26:16,317
You are mine, Etta Place.

221
00:26:16,424 --> 00:26:18,358
Mine!

222
00:26:18,460 --> 00:26:20,052
You hear me?

223
00:26:20,128 --> 00:26:23,427
Mine! All mine!

224
00:26:27,102 --> 00:26:30,230
Your soft, white flesh is mine.

225
00:26:30,305 --> 00:26:32,102
Soft.

226
00:26:32,173 --> 00:26:33,731
White.

227
00:26:42,751 --> 00:26:44,844
Meet the future!

228
00:26:45,487 --> 00:26:48,047
- Do you know what you're doing?
- Theoretically.

229
00:26:48,857 --> 00:26:52,054
Don't ever hit your mother with a shovel

230
00:26:52,127 --> 00:26:54,994
It leaves a dull impression on her mind!

231
00:26:59,301 --> 00:27:02,793
Raindrops keep falling on my head

232
00:27:03,305 --> 00:27:08,709
And just like the guy
whose feet are too big for his bed

233
00:27:08,777 --> 00:27:11,871
Nothing seems to fit, those

234
00:27:11,946 --> 00:27:16,679
Raindrops are falling on my head,
they keep falling

235
00:27:16,751 --> 00:27:21,484
So I just did me some talking to the sun

236
00:27:22,691 --> 00:27:27,993
And I said I didn't like
the way he got things done

237
00:27:28,096 --> 00:27:31,327
Sleeping on the job, those

238
00:27:31,399 --> 00:27:36,200
Raindrops are falling on my head,
they keep falling

239
00:27:36,304 --> 00:27:41,742
But there's one thing I know

240
00:27:41,810 --> 00:27:45,576
The blues they send to meet me

241
00:27:45,714 --> 00:27:48,740
Won't defeat me

242
00:27:48,817 --> 00:27:55,916
It won't be long
till happiness steps up to greet me

243
00:27:59,994 --> 00:28:03,054
Raindrops keep falling on my head

244
00:28:04,199 --> 00:28:09,660
But that doesn't mean
my eyes will soon be turning red

245
00:28:09,771 --> 00:28:13,002
Crying's not for me, cos

246
00:28:13,074 --> 00:28:17,238
I'm never gonna stop the rain by complaining

247
00:28:17,979 --> 00:28:21,471
Because I'm free

248
00:28:22,350 --> 00:28:24,648
Nothing's worrying me

249
00:29:36,357 --> 00:29:39,758
Raindrops are falling on my head

250
00:29:40,728 --> 00:29:46,360
But that doesn't mean
my eyes will soon be turning red

251
00:29:46,468 --> 00:29:49,767
Crying's not for me, cos

252
00:29:49,904 --> 00:29:54,307
I'm never gonna stop the rain by complaining

253
00:29:55,043 --> 00:29:59,377
Because I'm free

254
00:29:59,747 --> 00:30:03,046
Nothing's worrying

255
00:30:03,117 --> 00:30:06,109
Me

256
00:30:08,089 --> 00:30:11,149
You've come to get him for the Flyer?

257
00:30:11,259 --> 00:30:14,194
Can you believe I'm broke already?

258
00:30:14,295 --> 00:30:18,493
- Why is there never any money, Butch?
- Hell, I swear, Etta, I don't know.

259
00:30:18,566 --> 00:30:22,161
I've been working like a dog all my life
and I can't get a penny ahead.

260
00:30:22,270 --> 00:30:26,730
Sundance says it's cos you're a soft touch,
always taking expensive vacations,

261
00:30:26,808 --> 00:30:30,300
buying drinks for everyone,
and you're a rotten gambler.

262
00:30:30,378 --> 00:30:33,506
Well, that might have something to do with it!

263
00:30:48,229 --> 00:30:50,322
Butch?

264
00:30:50,899 --> 00:30:54,733
D'you ever wonder if I'd met you first,
we'd been the ones to get involved?

265
00:30:54,802 --> 00:30:57,737
We are involved, Etta. Don't you know that?

266
00:30:59,707 --> 00:31:05,543
You're riding on my bicycle. In some Arabian
countries that's the same as being married.

267
00:31:09,751 --> 00:31:11,810
Hey.

268
00:31:12,554 --> 00:31:15,455
- What're you doing?
- Stealing your woman.

269
00:31:18,760 --> 00:31:21,058
Take her. Take her.

270
00:31:22,764 --> 00:31:25,665
You're a romantic bastard. I'll give you that.

271
00:31:35,543 --> 00:31:40,139
- OK, open up in there.
- I work for Mr EH Harriman of the Union...

272
00:31:40,214 --> 00:31:42,739
- Hey, Woodcock!
- Butch?

273
00:31:42,817 --> 00:31:46,253
- You OK?
- Well, sort of.

274
00:31:46,354 --> 00:31:49,448
Hey, that's wonderful. Let's take a look at ya.

275
00:31:51,192 --> 00:31:57,153
Now, Butch, you gotta have more respect for
me than to think I'd fall for a stunt like that.

276
00:32:00,635 --> 00:32:05,470
- You can't wanna get blown up again?
- Butch, you know that if it were my money,

277
00:32:05,573 --> 00:32:08,872
there is nobody that I would
rather have steal it than you.

278
00:32:08,977 --> 00:32:14,176
But I am still in the employ of Mr
EH Harriman of the Union Pacific Railroad.

279
00:32:14,248 --> 00:32:16,512
- Start this train!
- Get back inside, lady.

280
00:32:16,618 --> 00:32:20,281
Oh, I'm not afraid of you.
I'm not afraid of anything.

281
00:32:20,388 --> 00:32:23,653
I'm a grandmother and a female,
and I've got my rights.

282
00:32:23,725 --> 00:32:27,491
- We've got no time for this.
- You can bull all the others, but not me!

283
00:32:27,595 --> 00:32:31,395
I've fought whiskey and gambling!
I can certainly fight you!

284
00:32:31,466 --> 00:32:33,024
We got no time for this!

285
00:32:33,334 --> 00:32:35,802
- Put down the gun, Sundance.
- Let go!

286
00:32:35,870 --> 00:32:39,237
- What you gonna do to her?
- Whatever you force me to.

287
00:32:39,307 --> 00:32:43,141
Leave her alone. You're after the money,
and the money's in here.

288
00:32:43,244 --> 00:32:47,613
All I want is for somebody to start this train.
Somebody! Please!

289
00:32:47,682 --> 00:32:52,745
- Open up or tell her goodbye!
- Our Father, who art in heaven,

290
00:32:52,854 --> 00:32:55,220
hallowed be thy name.

291
00:32:55,289 --> 00:32:58,884
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done,

292
00:32:58,960 --> 00:33:01,656
on earth, as it is in heaven.

293
00:33:01,729 --> 00:33:04,664
What am I gonna tell poor Mr Harriman?

294
00:33:07,869 --> 00:33:11,100
Woodcock,
what d'you have to do something like that for?

295
00:33:11,239 --> 00:33:15,539
Well, Butch, you blew the last one so easy
I just had to do something.

296
00:33:15,643 --> 00:33:17,702
Give me that, and get some more.

297
00:33:19,580 --> 00:33:21,275
A lot more!

298
00:33:22,583 --> 00:33:24,483
Well, that oughta do it.

299
00:33:45,339 --> 00:33:48,604
Think you used enough dynamite there,
Butch?

300
00:34:43,064 --> 00:34:44,793
What the hell is that?

301
00:35:07,822 --> 00:35:11,383
Whatever they're selling, I don't want it.

302
00:35:20,001 --> 00:35:22,299
Will you leave it!

303
00:35:27,975 --> 00:35:30,034
Come on!

304
00:35:48,329 --> 00:35:50,263
- Hey, Butch.
- What?

305
00:35:50,331 --> 00:35:52,026
They're very good.

306
00:35:54,635 --> 00:35:56,694
Split up!

307
00:36:09,717 --> 00:36:12,151
- How many of them are following us?
- All of them.

308
00:36:12,253 --> 00:36:16,622
All of them?
What's the matter with those guys?!

309
00:37:46,147 --> 00:37:49,412
I think we lost them. D'you think we lost them?

310
00:37:50,151 --> 00:37:52,779
- No.
- Neither do I.

311
00:38:10,104 --> 00:38:10,137
Take our horses and keep them out of sight.

312
00:38:10,137 --> 00:38:12,867
Take our horses and keep them out of sight.

313
00:38:12,974 --> 00:38:15,841
- Where's Sweetface?
- Just inside. Trouble?

314
00:38:17,411 --> 00:38:21,871
Listen, you dirty old man, I know you're
a lying thief, but who'd know it to look at ya?

315
00:38:21,983 --> 00:38:25,419
Get out front fast. You seen us
ride through town five minutes ago.

316
00:38:25,486 --> 00:38:28,683
You do this right,
I'll get you an old dog to kick.

317
00:38:29,423 --> 00:38:31,948
Here, room nine. The top of the stairs.

318
00:38:43,204 --> 00:38:45,900
My beloved's proud

319
00:38:46,907 --> 00:38:50,775
Hey, you're driving me crazy
staring out the window like that.

320
00:38:50,845 --> 00:38:53,473
I swear to you Sweetface can handle it easy.

321
00:38:53,581 --> 00:38:57,108
He wouldn't dare louse me up,
he's that scared of me.

322
00:39:03,257 --> 00:39:08,889
How can I give Agnes the concentration she
deserves with you looking out the window?

323
00:39:08,996 --> 00:39:12,090
Butch, you're really something,
you know that?

324
00:39:14,335 --> 00:39:18,294
Could you be a bit more specific, Agnes?

325
00:39:18,406 --> 00:39:20,465
Butch!

326
00:39:25,913 --> 00:39:28,507
OK, Sweetface, give them a nice smile.

327
00:39:29,316 --> 00:39:31,409
Come on.

328
00:39:32,553 --> 00:39:34,248
Oh, that's a nice touch.

329
00:39:34,321 --> 00:39:39,554
You know, I swear, if he told me I rode
out of town ten minutes ago, I'd believe him.

330
00:39:41,862 --> 00:39:43,921
And there they go.

331
00:39:52,039 --> 00:39:55,133
No, no, no. Don't ask me to stay.

332
00:40:03,350 --> 00:40:07,116
You're the only real man I ever met.
You know that, Butch?

333
00:40:08,055 --> 00:40:12,321
It's notjust cos of all that money
you got to spend on people.

334
00:40:12,393 --> 00:40:16,591
It's you. The way you're always
looking to see am I happy or not.

335
00:40:17,364 --> 00:40:20,663
A lot of the other girls,
they might want you just for

336
00:40:20,734 --> 00:40:23,726
when you got lots of money
to spend on people.

337
00:40:23,804 --> 00:40:25,567
Me, I...

338
00:40:25,673 --> 00:40:33,546
I don't care about clothes
and money and jewels and furs.

339
00:40:35,516 --> 00:40:40,954
Things like that.
Lots of the other girls do, but I never did.

340
00:40:41,021 --> 00:40:43,114
I always said "Agnes..."

341
00:41:01,742 --> 00:41:03,710
Don't move!

342
00:41:04,044 --> 00:41:06,342
Stand up. Put your hands up.

343
00:41:07,314 --> 00:41:09,179
Higher!

344
00:41:10,718 --> 00:41:12,777
Now turn around and...

345
00:41:17,558 --> 00:41:20,186
Get our horses and come on back here.

346
00:41:28,202 --> 00:41:31,262
Get outta here. Get outta here.

347
00:41:31,438 --> 00:41:33,531
Get out!

348
00:41:36,010 --> 00:41:39,571
Go on! Get outta here, you fatheaded beast!

349
00:41:41,215 --> 00:41:44,776
- Come on!
- You're the fatheaded beast. Quit shouting.

350
00:41:45,953 --> 00:41:48,444
Boy, somebody sure trained them.

351
00:42:17,251 --> 00:42:18,775
Which way?

352
00:42:18,852 --> 00:42:22,845
It doesn't matter. I don't know
where we've been and I've just been there.

353
00:42:22,923 --> 00:42:25,483
They can't follow us. We're safe.

354
00:42:25,793 --> 00:42:27,727
You really think so?

355
00:42:27,828 --> 00:42:30,319
I will if you will.

356
00:42:58,692 --> 00:43:01,627
How long you figure we been watching?

357
00:43:02,263 --> 00:43:04,322
Oh, a while.

358
00:43:17,044 --> 00:43:20,241
How long before
you figure they're not after us?

359
00:43:20,314 --> 00:43:22,373
A while longer.

360
00:43:24,785 --> 00:43:27,310
How come you're so talkative?

361
00:43:28,756 --> 00:43:31,281
Just naturally blabby, I guess.

362
00:43:35,296 --> 00:43:37,992
I haven't done so much riding
since I quit rustling.

363
00:43:38,098 --> 00:43:42,899
That's a miserable occupation.
Dusk to dawn, no sleep, rotten food.

364
00:43:47,141 --> 00:43:49,006
Hey?

365
00:43:49,777 --> 00:43:51,870
I see it.

366
00:43:55,582 --> 00:43:57,880
Torches, you think?

367
00:43:57,951 --> 00:44:00,112
Maybe. Maybe lanterns.

368
00:44:01,789 --> 00:44:03,882
They're following our path.

369
00:44:05,192 --> 00:44:07,422
Dead on it.

370
00:44:07,528 --> 00:44:11,521
I couldn't do that. Could you do that?
How can they do that?!

371
00:44:13,167 --> 00:44:15,294
Who are those guys?

372
00:44:26,947 --> 00:44:29,313
- Sure it'll work?
- It'll work.

373
00:44:29,383 --> 00:44:33,149
- That's what you said about Sweetface!
- This'll work.

374
00:44:58,011 --> 00:45:02,072
Once they divide up, we take them.
No trouble. Right?

375
00:45:02,616 --> 00:45:04,550
Maybe.

376
00:45:04,618 --> 00:45:07,985
Boy, for a gunman,
you're one hell of a pessimist.

377
00:45:09,223 --> 00:45:12,420
They ought to get to
where we split up anytime.

378
00:45:14,795 --> 00:45:17,263
They're just about there.

379
00:45:20,067 --> 00:45:22,797
How many of them you think'll come our way?

380
00:45:24,071 --> 00:45:27,199
I wish we had rifles. I mean, they got rifles.

381
00:45:27,274 --> 00:45:30,004
But we got surprise on our side, right?

382
00:45:35,816 --> 00:45:38,910
Well, so far they're doing what we want.

383
00:45:42,656 --> 00:45:45,591
You think we ought to take them from up here?

384
00:45:50,831 --> 00:45:53,425
Kid... look,
you know this work better than I do.

385
00:45:53,500 --> 00:45:57,698
Is it best here or maybe down there,
closer to the trail?

386
00:46:03,744 --> 00:46:05,837
Dammit!

387
00:46:07,748 --> 00:46:10,012
They're not going for it.

388
00:46:12,753 --> 00:46:15,051
Who are those guys?

389
00:46:15,722 --> 00:46:17,815
I don't know.

390
00:46:18,425 --> 00:46:21,121
- I don't know!
- We gotta do something and shake them.

391
00:46:21,228 --> 00:46:27,030
Whatever it is that you come up with is fine
with me. But whatever it is, it better be now!

392
00:46:38,545 --> 00:46:39,978
- Ray...
- What're you doing?

393
00:46:40,080 --> 00:46:43,743
- Hold on. Easy, Ray.
- What the hell do you mean, take it easy?!

394
00:46:43,851 --> 00:46:47,548
- You said you'd never come to my territory.
- We haven't, Ray. We haven't!

395
00:46:47,654 --> 00:46:50,680
Just cos we were friendly
doesn't allow you to break in.

396
00:46:50,757 --> 00:46:53,692
What would happen to me
if we was to be seen together?

397
00:46:53,760 --> 00:46:56,251
I'm too old to hunt up anotherjob!

398
00:46:57,664 --> 00:47:00,064
You could at least have drawn your guns!

399
00:47:00,133 --> 00:47:02,897
Listen to Butch.
He's trying to tell you something.

400
00:47:02,970 --> 00:47:05,165
All right. What do you want?

401
00:47:05,272 --> 00:47:08,537
A couple of things. We wanna enlist, Ray.

402
00:47:08,609 --> 00:47:12,375
You know, in the army.
Right away! Go fight the Spanish.

403
00:47:17,518 --> 00:47:20,146
Oh, you're crazy. You are crazy.

404
00:47:21,021 --> 00:47:23,751
You are both of you crazy!

405
00:47:23,824 --> 00:47:27,157
They'd throw you in jail
for a thousand years each!

406
00:47:32,199 --> 00:47:35,134
Come on, Sundance. Start trussing my feet.

407
00:47:37,971 --> 00:47:42,635
Here, you've seen these before. Come on! I'm
not gonna take the chance someone saw you.

408
00:47:42,743 --> 00:47:44,802
Ray, we're serious about this.

409
00:47:44,912 --> 00:47:47,437
- You are known outlaws.
- We quit.

410
00:47:47,548 --> 00:47:50,039
- Quit!
- That's the point, we would. Too tight?

411
00:47:50,150 --> 00:47:54,246
No, that's all right. There's hankies
in the top drawer you can use to gag me.

412
00:47:54,354 --> 00:47:57,118
Oh, this'd work. This'd work, Ray.

413
00:47:57,190 --> 00:48:02,150
You trust us and the government trusts you,
so anything you tell them, they gotta believe it.

414
00:48:02,229 --> 00:48:06,791
You've never done a dishonest thing in your
life and what are you, pushing 60? We'd quit.

415
00:48:06,867 --> 00:48:10,030
They'd drop all the charges.
We'd fight till the war is over.

416
00:48:10,137 --> 00:48:14,471
- They don't even have to make us officers.
- That's some proposition.

417
00:48:14,575 --> 00:48:18,409
I mean, they forget all about
the years of thieving and robbing?

418
00:48:18,478 --> 00:48:23,006
They take you into the army,
which is what you want in the first place.

419
00:48:25,052 --> 00:48:28,488
There's something out there that scares you,
huh?

420
00:48:29,957 --> 00:48:35,418
It's too late. Shoulda let yourselves get killed
a long time ago while you had the chance.

421
00:48:35,495 --> 00:48:41,832
See, you may be the biggest thing ever hit
this area, but you're still two-bit outlaws!

422
00:48:41,902 --> 00:48:45,429
I never met a soul more affable than you,
or faster than the Kid,

423
00:48:45,505 --> 00:48:51,466
but you're still nothing but two-bit outlaws
on the dodge. It's over! Don't you get that?

424
00:48:51,578 --> 00:48:57,881
Your times is over and you're gonna die
bloody! And all you can do is choose where.

425
00:48:58,719 --> 00:49:01,415
I'm sorry. I'm getting mean in my old age.

426
00:49:02,089 --> 00:49:04,182
Come on! Shut me up, Sundance.

427
00:51:24,662 --> 00:51:26,562
Ah, you're wasting your time.

428
00:51:26,864 --> 00:51:30,630
- They can't track us over rock.
- Tell them that.

429
00:51:57,028 --> 00:51:59,496
They're beginning to get on my nerves.

430
00:52:01,098 --> 00:52:03,191
Who are those guys?

431
00:52:05,169 --> 00:52:10,072
You remember the time you and me and Etta
went to Denver that summer for a vacation?

432
00:52:10,174 --> 00:52:14,167
Glad you brought that up.
An important topic, considering our situation.

433
00:52:14,245 --> 00:52:17,772
- The night we went gambling. Remember?
- We had dinner at the hotel.

434
00:52:17,848 --> 00:52:23,514
Etta had roast beef and I had chicken. If I can
remember what you had, I'll die a happy man!

435
00:52:24,221 --> 00:52:26,280
- Look out there.
- What?

436
00:52:27,591 --> 00:52:31,721
We got to talking to some gambler that night
and he told us about an Indian.

437
00:52:31,829 --> 00:52:36,926
A full-blooded Indian, except he called
himself with an English name. Sir somebody.

438
00:52:37,034 --> 00:52:40,663
- Lord Baltimore?
- That's right. And he could track anybody.

439
00:52:40,738 --> 00:52:43,206
Over anything, day or night.

440
00:52:43,274 --> 00:52:45,139
So?

441
00:52:46,043 --> 00:52:48,273
The guy on the ground, I think it's him.

442
00:52:53,684 --> 00:52:57,279
No, Baltimore works out of Oklahoma.
He's strictly an Oklahoma man.

443
00:52:57,355 --> 00:53:01,314
I don't know where we are,
but it sure as hell isn't Oklahoma.

444
00:53:01,425 --> 00:53:03,484
Aw, it couldn't be him.

445
00:53:08,532 --> 00:53:10,625
It couldn't be him.

446
00:53:11,669 --> 00:53:13,728
I guess.

447
00:53:15,473 --> 00:53:18,306
Whoever it is, it sure the hell is somebody.

448
00:53:49,607 --> 00:53:53,270
Dammit! Don't they get tired?
Don't they get hungry?

449
00:53:54,278 --> 00:53:57,008
- They gotta be.
- Why don't they slow up?

450
00:53:57,114 --> 00:54:01,778
Hell, they could go faster. At least that'd be
a change. They don't even break formation.

451
00:54:01,886 --> 00:54:03,945
Do something!

452
00:54:38,722 --> 00:54:41,190
- Kid?
- What?

453
00:54:42,326 --> 00:54:44,590
Who's the best lawman?

454
00:54:45,729 --> 00:54:49,790
Best? How?
You mean toughest, or easiest to bribe?

455
00:54:50,434 --> 00:54:52,129
Toughest.

456
00:54:53,471 --> 00:54:55,132
Joe Lefors.

457
00:54:55,973 --> 00:54:58,032
Gotta be.

458
00:55:01,545 --> 00:55:04,981
Lefors never leaves Wyoming. Never.
You know that.

459
00:55:06,050 --> 00:55:08,348
He always wears a white skimmer.

460
00:55:08,419 --> 00:55:12,617
That's how you tell it's Joe Lefors
cos he wears a white straw hat.

461
00:55:14,458 --> 00:55:16,551
Look at that guy out front.

462
00:55:36,280 --> 00:55:38,475
Jeez, who are those guys?

463
00:55:44,054 --> 00:55:46,022
Come on!

464
00:55:46,090 --> 00:55:48,183
On your feet, you dumbhead.

465
00:56:31,936 --> 00:56:34,496
Go on! Get outta here! Go on!

466
00:56:35,973 --> 00:56:37,964
What if they don't follow the horse?

467
00:56:38,075 --> 00:56:41,636
You're the brains, Butch.
You'll think of something.

468
00:58:09,094 --> 00:58:11,187
Dammit!

469
00:58:24,642 --> 00:58:27,475
The way I figure it, we can either fight or give.

470
00:58:27,545 --> 00:58:30,912
- If we give, we go to jail.
- I've been there already.

471
00:58:31,816 --> 00:58:35,809
But if we fight, they can stay
right where they are and starve us out.

472
00:58:35,887 --> 00:58:40,324
Or go for position, shoot us. Might even
get a rock slide started and get us that way.

473
00:58:40,425 --> 00:58:42,416
What else can they do?

474
00:58:42,494 --> 00:58:45,292
They could surrender,
but I wouldn't count on that.

475
00:58:46,498 --> 00:58:49,228
They're going for position all right.

476
00:58:50,168 --> 00:58:52,466
Better get ready.

477
00:58:54,839 --> 00:58:59,833
Kid, the next time I say let's go someplace
like Bolivia, let's go someplace like Bolivia.

478
00:58:59,911 --> 00:59:01,344
Next time...

479
00:59:03,348 --> 00:59:05,248
Ready?

480
00:59:06,584 --> 00:59:08,677
No, we'll jump.

481
00:59:13,057 --> 00:59:16,288
- Like hell we will.
- No, it'll be OK,

482
00:59:16,361 --> 00:59:19,455
if we're not squished to death.
They'll never follow us.

483
00:59:19,531 --> 00:59:23,092
- How do you know?
- Would you jump if you didn't have to?

484
00:59:23,168 --> 00:59:27,070
- I have to and I'm not gonna.
- Well, we got to, otherwise we're dead.

485
00:59:27,138 --> 00:59:29,800
They'll just have to go back
the same way they come.

486
00:59:29,908 --> 00:59:32,308
- Just one clear shot.
- Come on.

487
00:59:32,377 --> 00:59:34,072
- We got to!
- Get away from me.

488
00:59:34,145 --> 00:59:35,942
- Why?
- I wanna fight them!

489
00:59:36,014 --> 00:59:37,481
- They'll kill us!
- Maybe.

490
00:59:37,549 --> 00:59:40,074
- You wanna die?
- Do you?

491
00:59:40,952 --> 00:59:43,614
All right. I'll jump first.

492
00:59:43,721 --> 00:59:45,586
- No.
- Then you jump first.

493
00:59:45,690 --> 00:59:47,419
- No, I said.
- What's the matter?

494
00:59:47,625 --> 00:59:49,718
I can't swim!

495
00:59:59,404 --> 01:00:02,965
Why, are you crazy?
The fall will probably kill ya!

496
01:00:26,331 --> 01:00:29,630
- You're drowning me!
- I can't help it! I can't swim!

497
01:00:29,734 --> 01:00:33,636
- Kid, I'll kill ya! You're choking me!
- I can't swim!

498
01:00:33,738 --> 01:00:36,935
I'm telling you, if I drown,
I swear I'll kill you!

499
01:00:37,175 --> 01:00:40,406
Never said I was a great swimmer.

500
01:00:45,149 --> 01:00:48,846
You're choking me! You're choking me!

501
01:00:49,487 --> 01:00:51,580
You don't have to choke me!

502
01:00:52,991 --> 01:00:55,050
Kid, let go of my throat!

503
01:01:22,854 --> 01:01:25,482
The papers said they had you.

504
01:01:26,457 --> 01:01:31,019
- Was it Lefors? Did they say?
- Joe Lefors? I think so.

505
01:01:31,095 --> 01:01:33,723
- And their tracker?
- Tracker?

506
01:01:33,831 --> 01:01:37,699
- Was it Lord Baltimore?
- I think so. The paper's inside.

507
01:01:44,943 --> 01:01:47,275
You got enough to feed us?

508
01:01:47,345 --> 01:01:49,438
Don't you know I do?

509
01:01:50,348 --> 01:01:54,114
- They said you were dead.
- Don't make a big thing out of it.

510
01:01:57,422 --> 01:01:59,686
No, make a big thing out of it.

511
01:02:04,929 --> 01:02:06,829
Hey!

512
01:02:07,632 --> 01:02:10,123
It was Baltimore and Lefors.

513
01:02:15,873 --> 01:02:17,738
What?

514
01:02:18,977 --> 01:02:20,706
- You know who else?
- Who?

515
01:02:20,778 --> 01:02:23,110
- Jeff Car, George Hiatt.
- Hiatt?

516
01:02:23,181 --> 01:02:25,274
TT Kelliher.

517
01:02:28,786 --> 01:02:32,381
Jeez, we lucked out getting away.
You know that?

518
01:02:34,726 --> 01:02:38,287
But why would these guys join up
and take after us, though?

519
01:02:38,363 --> 01:02:41,298
Forget it.
A bunch like that won't stay together long.

520
01:02:41,366 --> 01:02:45,063
- They will, if Mr Harriman has his way.
- Who?

521
01:02:45,169 --> 01:02:50,402
EH Harriman of the Union Pacific Railroad.
He resents the way you've picked on him,

522
01:02:50,541 --> 01:02:54,136
so he's outfitted a special train
and hired special employees.

523
01:02:54,746 --> 01:02:57,306
You've spent the last two days
avoiding them.

524
01:02:57,382 --> 01:03:01,478
It's really sort of flattering,
if you wanna think about it that way.

525
01:03:01,552 --> 01:03:06,421
- A setup like that costs more than we took.
- Apparently he can afford it.

526
01:03:08,960 --> 01:03:11,019
That crazy Harriman.

527
01:03:13,131 --> 01:03:14,996
That's bad business!

528
01:03:15,099 --> 01:03:20,298
How long d'you think I'd stay in operation
if every time I pulled ajob it cost me money?

529
01:03:20,371 --> 01:03:25,638
If he'd pay me what he's spending to make me
stop robbing him, I'd stop robbing him!

530
01:03:28,146 --> 01:03:31,013
You probably inherited every penny you got!

531
01:03:31,749 --> 01:03:35,913
- Inherited guys. What the hell do they know?
- You say they're hired permanent?

532
01:03:36,754 --> 01:03:39,018
No. Just till they kill you.

533
01:03:48,766 --> 01:03:51,929
That means they're still after us, Butch.

534
01:03:52,003 --> 01:03:55,234
And it's gonna be
the same thing all over again.

535
01:03:59,944 --> 01:04:03,038
They'll show up here, sooner or later.

536
01:04:20,031 --> 01:04:22,090
Hey, Etta.

537
01:04:22,200 --> 01:04:23,997
I'll get you some more.

538
01:04:24,068 --> 01:04:27,799
Butch and me have been talking it all over.

539
01:04:27,872 --> 01:04:31,433
Wherever the hell Bolivia is,
that's where we're off to.

540
01:04:31,509 --> 01:04:36,503
Yeah, we'll go down there and play it safe.
Maybe keep our hand in a little bit.

541
01:04:37,982 --> 01:04:41,110
- Butch speaks some Spanish.
- I can wrestle with a menu OK.

542
01:04:41,219 --> 01:04:43,312
And you speak it good.

543
01:04:44,722 --> 01:04:47,213
It'd be good cover going with a woman.

544
01:04:48,226 --> 01:04:50,319
No one expects it.

545
01:04:51,596 --> 01:04:53,655
We could travel safer.

546
01:04:56,400 --> 01:04:59,836
What I'm saying is if you wanna go,
I won't stop you.

547
01:04:59,904 --> 01:05:03,101
But the minute you start
to whine or make a nuisance,

548
01:05:03,207 --> 01:05:06,938
I don't care where we are,
I'm dumping you flat.

549
01:05:07,044 --> 01:05:10,810
Don't sugarcoat it like that, Kid.
Tell her straight.

550
01:05:15,686 --> 01:05:21,283
I'm 26 and I'm single and a schoolteacher,
and that's the bottom of the pit.

551
01:05:21,425 --> 01:05:25,088
And the only excitement I've known
is here with me now.

552
01:05:26,030 --> 01:05:31,696
So I'll go with you and I won't whine, and
I'll sew your socks and stitch your wounds,

553
01:05:31,769 --> 01:05:35,296
and I'll do anything you ask of me,
except one thing.

554
01:05:36,507 --> 01:05:38,668
I won't watch you die.

555
01:05:38,743 --> 01:05:41,473
I'll miss that scene, if you don't mind.

556
01:06:15,613 --> 01:06:18,377
The future's all yours, ya lousy bicycles!

557
01:11:23,687 --> 01:11:26,212
Well, you know, it could be worse.

558
01:11:27,057 --> 01:11:30,823
You get a lot more for your money in Bolivia.
I checked on it.

559
01:11:30,895 --> 01:11:35,025
What could they have here
that you could possibly wanna buy?

560
01:11:40,671 --> 01:11:42,901
Jeez, all Bolivia can't look like this.

561
01:11:43,040 --> 01:11:47,500
How do you know? This might be
the garden spot of the whole country.

562
01:11:48,746 --> 01:11:54,446
People may travel hundreds of miles just
to get to this spot where we're standing now.

563
01:11:54,518 --> 01:11:57,681
This might be the Atlantic City,
New Jersey of all Bolivia.

564
01:11:57,755 --> 01:12:03,523
I know a lot more about Bolivia than you
know about Atlantic City, I can tell you that.

565
01:12:04,461 --> 01:12:06,520
You do, huh?

566
01:12:07,431 --> 01:12:09,296
I was born there.

567
01:12:09,366 --> 01:12:11,459
I was born in New Jersey.

568
01:12:12,169 --> 01:12:15,661
- Brought up there. So...
- You're from the East. I didn't know.

569
01:12:15,739 --> 01:12:18,833
The total tonnage of what
you don't know is enough to...

570
01:12:18,909 --> 01:12:22,743
- I'm not sure we're accomplishing anything.
- Listen!

571
01:12:22,880 --> 01:12:27,180
Your job is to back me up,
because you'd starve without me.

572
01:12:27,952 --> 01:12:30,477
And, you, yourjob is to shut up!

573
01:12:34,892 --> 01:12:39,192
Well, he'll feel a lot better
after he's robbed a couple of banks.

574
01:12:43,801 --> 01:12:45,894
Bolivia!

575
01:12:55,546 --> 01:13:01,348
Hell, it's just a bank like any other bank.
Gotta move in slowly, check out everything.

576
01:13:02,586 --> 01:13:06,989
- The thing to remember...
- Don't tell me how to rob a bank! I know how!

577
01:13:07,691 --> 01:13:13,095
Boy, a few dark clouds appear on your
horizon, you just go all to pieces, don't you?

578
01:13:33,617 --> 01:13:39,317
Buenos días, señores, Les puedo servir
en algo? Ordenen, por favor, inmediatamente,

579
01:13:40,958 --> 01:13:43,017
Quieren hacer algún depósito?

580
01:13:45,329 --> 01:13:50,528
Si quieren abrir alguna cuenta, vean al cajero,
Inmediatamente los atendemos,

581
01:13:56,974 --> 01:13:58,839
Señor?

582
01:14:09,820 --> 01:14:11,913
Adiós,

583
01:14:12,189 --> 01:14:14,020
This is a robbery.

584
01:14:14,091 --> 01:14:16,423
Esto es un robo,

585
01:14:17,428 --> 01:14:19,487
Esto es un robo,

586
01:14:25,669 --> 01:14:27,660
This is a unison recitation.

587
01:14:27,771 --> 01:14:30,865
I'm not doing this.
He claimed he knew the damn language!

588
01:14:30,974 --> 01:14:36,002
We've been over this before. Your line
of work requires a specialized vocabulary.

589
01:14:36,080 --> 01:14:39,880
- I got nervous. I forgot the words. Shoot me!
- You've had worse ideas lately!

590
01:14:40,184 --> 01:14:42,243
Raise your hands.

591
01:14:44,621 --> 01:14:46,111
Las manos arriba,

592
01:14:46,223 --> 01:14:48,316
Raise them.

593
01:14:49,226 --> 01:14:51,194
Arriba,

594
01:14:51,261 --> 01:14:53,456
All of you, back against the wall.

595
01:14:53,997 --> 01:14:56,056
Todos ustedes,

596
01:14:56,834 --> 01:14:59,997
and then..."arrísmense" a la pared,

597
01:15:01,739 --> 01:15:03,832
Give me the money.

598
01:15:09,046 --> 01:15:11,276
Give me the money.

599
01:15:11,915 --> 01:15:14,008
Give me the money.

600
01:15:15,452 --> 01:15:19,149
This is not going to work and we'll be up
all night until you get this.

601
01:15:19,256 --> 01:15:21,349
Now, give me the money.

602
01:15:25,963 --> 01:15:28,898
It's on the tip of my tongue, Etta. I swear it.

603
01:15:31,568 --> 01:15:34,560
Butch, are you still thinking in there?

604
01:15:34,671 --> 01:15:36,639
What the hell else is there to do?

605
01:15:37,307 --> 01:15:39,275
Try this one.

606
01:15:39,343 --> 01:15:41,709
Where is the safe? Open it.

607
01:15:42,346 --> 01:15:44,473
Dónde es,,,?

608
01:15:48,585 --> 01:15:50,678
That's a hard one.

609
01:15:52,890 --> 01:15:55,256
Dónde está la caja? Ábrala!

610
01:15:56,193 --> 01:15:58,093
That's very good, Butch.

611
01:15:59,096 --> 01:16:01,155
You're a good teacher, Etta.

612
01:16:02,166 --> 01:16:04,566
- Esto es un robo!
- Un robo?

613
01:16:10,140 --> 01:16:12,005
Manos a,,,

614
01:16:12,509 --> 01:16:14,977
Manos,,,

615
01:16:21,919 --> 01:16:24,615
- Manos arriba!
- They got them up! Skip on down.

616
01:16:24,822 --> 01:16:26,289
- Arriba!
- Skip on down!

617
01:16:26,356 --> 01:16:31,953
- Todos ustedes "arrísmense" a la pared,
- They're against the wall already!

618
01:16:32,563 --> 01:16:35,691
Dónde,,,
Ah, you're so damn smart, you read it!

619
01:16:47,010 --> 01:16:49,740
- Lot of good you did.
- You didn't help.

620
01:16:49,813 --> 01:16:52,338
You ain't any good without a crib sheet.

621
01:16:59,456 --> 01:17:01,583
Bandidos!

622
01:17:09,066 --> 01:17:12,593
- For God's sake, don't drop the money!
- I won't!

623
01:17:12,669 --> 01:17:15,365
- Voy a traer al comisario,
- Sí, vamos!

624
01:17:15,439 --> 01:17:17,339
- Su nombre?
- Evaristo,

625
01:17:17,407 --> 01:17:19,034
Evaristo qué?

626
01:17:19,142 --> 01:17:21,975
Comandante,
dos hombres acaban de asaltar el banco,

627
01:17:22,045 --> 01:17:25,344
- Quiénes eran?
- Dos yanquis y una muchacha,

628
01:17:25,415 --> 01:17:27,849
Se llevaron todo el dinero y mi pistola,

629
01:17:27,951 --> 01:17:30,852
Vamonos! Vengan ustedes, a los caballos!

630
01:18:23,106 --> 01:18:24,801
Isn't that a pretty sight?

631
01:18:28,445 --> 01:18:32,040
We're back in business,
boys and girls, just like the old days.

632
01:22:59,282 --> 01:23:01,147
- Jose!
- Sí, señor,

633
01:23:01,218 --> 01:23:03,413
We should stay, get him and be done with it.

634
01:23:03,520 --> 01:23:07,547
Yeah, but what if we lose? We saw him
with two guys, but what if he's got 20?

635
01:23:07,624 --> 01:23:11,321
- You don't know for sure it's Lefors.
- I'm a hell of a guesser.

636
01:23:11,394 --> 01:23:14,830
He can't arrest you here.
It's a foreign country. Or take you back.

637
01:23:14,931 --> 01:23:18,162
He's not gonna take anybody back.
He wants to finish us here.

638
01:23:18,235 --> 01:23:21,227
He'll wait for us to pull ajob,
then hunt us like before.

639
01:23:21,338 --> 01:23:26,970
And if he misses us, he'll wait for the next
job. Let's finish it now, one way or the other.

640
01:23:27,978 --> 01:23:31,436
He's gotta wait for us, right?
To pull anotherjob?

641
01:23:32,048 --> 01:23:34,915
Well, what if there isn't anotherjob?

642
01:23:34,985 --> 01:23:38,648
I mean, he can't arrest us
and he can't take us outta here.

643
01:23:38,755 --> 01:23:43,124
We'll drive him crazy.
We'll outlast the bastard. We'll go straight!

644
01:23:43,226 --> 01:23:45,319
So you want jobs?

645
01:23:46,229 --> 01:23:51,599
You're from the US of A
and you are seeking after employment.

646
01:23:51,668 --> 01:23:57,607
Well, you couldn't have picked a more out of
the way place in all Bolivia, I'll tell you that.

647
01:23:58,642 --> 01:24:00,735
Gracias, Jesús,

648
01:24:00,810 --> 01:24:07,181
Ordinarily, you've got to wait to work
for Percy Garris, but this ain't ordinarily.

649
01:24:07,284 --> 01:24:08,649
Bingo.

650
01:24:08,752 --> 01:24:13,246
- You mean there are jobs?
- Yes, there are jobs.
There are lots ofjobs.

651
01:24:13,356 --> 01:24:15,551
Don't you wanna know why?

652
01:24:15,625 --> 01:24:17,684
Yeah. Why?

653
01:24:17,794 --> 01:24:19,421
Dammy.

654
01:24:19,496 --> 01:24:22,624
Because I cannot promise to pay you.

655
01:24:23,400 --> 01:24:25,868
Don't you wanna know why?

656
01:24:25,969 --> 01:24:28,028
OK. Why?

657
01:24:29,439 --> 01:24:33,876
On account of the payroll thieves,
fellow citizens.

658
01:24:33,977 --> 01:24:38,971
You see, every mine around
gets its payroll from La Paz.

659
01:24:39,649 --> 01:24:43,176
And every mine around
gets its payroll held up.

660
01:24:44,220 --> 01:24:47,781
Some say it's the Bolivian bandits and...

661
01:24:48,692 --> 01:24:53,186
some say that it's the "Bandidos Yanquis."

662
01:24:53,697 --> 01:24:55,790
Could I see that?

663
01:25:00,737 --> 01:25:04,468
Fairly nice-Iooking piece.
Can you hit anything?

664
01:25:05,342 --> 01:25:07,435
Sometimes.

665
01:25:16,019 --> 01:25:18,078
Hit that.

666
01:25:23,693 --> 01:25:28,062
No, no, son. No, son.
I just wanna know can you shoot.

667
01:25:28,131 --> 01:25:30,224
Put your piece in your hand...

668
01:25:31,468 --> 01:25:33,527
and shoot.

669
01:25:44,714 --> 01:25:46,648
Dammy.

670
01:25:46,716 --> 01:25:48,684
Can I move?

671
01:25:48,752 --> 01:25:51,653
Move? What the hell you mean move?

672
01:25:57,127 --> 01:25:59,652
- I'm better when I move.
- Yeah.

673
01:26:00,930 --> 01:26:06,732
Well, considering that I'm desperate
and you are just what I'm looking for,

674
01:26:06,803 --> 01:26:11,365
on top of which you stem from the US of A,
we start tomorrow morning.

675
01:26:11,508 --> 01:26:13,976
- You mean we gotjobs?
- Payroll guard.

676
01:26:14,611 --> 01:26:16,078
Dammy.

677
01:26:16,146 --> 01:26:17,807
Vámonos a trabajar!

678
01:26:17,914 --> 01:26:20,144
Hey, Chusto! Chusto!

679
01:26:20,216 --> 01:26:24,949
Oh, don't you remember
sweet Betsy from Pike?

680
01:26:25,021 --> 01:26:29,390
Crossed the high mountains
with her lover, Ike

681
01:26:29,526 --> 01:26:33,485
Two yoke of oxen and a big yeller dog

682
01:26:33,563 --> 01:26:37,226
A tall Shanghai rooster and one spotted hog

683
01:26:37,333 --> 01:26:41,565
Toodle-dang hoodie aye-doh,
toodle-dang hoodie ay

684
01:26:41,638 --> 01:26:45,938
Toodle-dang hoodie aye-doh,
toodle-dang hoodie ay

685
01:26:46,009 --> 01:26:49,775
The Shanghai ran off and the cattle all died

686
01:26:49,846 --> 01:26:51,939
Last piece of bacon that morning...

687
01:26:52,015 --> 01:26:54,347
I think they're in the trees up ahead.

688
01:26:54,417 --> 01:26:57,580
- In the bushes on the left.
- They're in the trees up ahead!

689
01:26:57,654 --> 01:27:00,623
You take the trees, I'll take the bushes.

690
01:27:00,723 --> 01:27:03,715
Will you two beginners cut it out!

691
01:27:04,160 --> 01:27:07,721
Well, we're just trying to spot an ambush,
Mr Garris.

692
01:27:07,797 --> 01:27:09,594
Morons.

693
01:27:09,666 --> 01:27:12,567
I've got morons on my team.

694
01:27:12,635 --> 01:27:16,264
Nobody is going to rob us
going down the mountain!

695
01:27:16,372 --> 01:27:19,341
We have got no money
going down the mountain!

696
01:27:19,409 --> 01:27:23,846
When we have got the money,
on the way back,

697
01:27:24,080 --> 01:27:26,173
then you can sweat.

698
01:27:26,616 --> 01:27:28,675
Bingo.

699
01:27:53,877 --> 01:27:56,368
We hit this place in June, didn't we?

700
01:28:09,092 --> 01:28:10,992
Jones!

701
01:28:11,528 --> 01:28:13,462
Give me a hand over here.

702
01:28:13,530 --> 01:28:15,657
Who am I? Smith or Jones?

703
01:28:16,266 --> 01:28:18,234
Live!

704
01:28:35,018 --> 01:28:38,215
'Bout a half-hour more
and we can start to worry.

705
01:28:39,022 --> 01:28:43,425
As soon as we get to the pass up there.
We'll be all right till then.

706
01:28:44,727 --> 01:28:48,720
- They might try something here.
- Nah. Better cover up there.

707
01:28:50,633 --> 01:28:55,627
You got to relax, you fellas.
You got to get used to Bolivian ways.

708
01:28:55,939 --> 01:28:58,339
You got to go easy. Dammy!

709
01:28:58,875 --> 01:29:00,103
Like I do.

710
01:29:00,176 --> 01:29:04,476
Course,
you probably think I'm crazy, but I'm not.

711
01:29:05,648 --> 01:29:07,741
Bingo. I'm colorful.

712
01:29:08,484 --> 01:29:13,353
That's what happens when you live
ten years alone in Bolivia. You get colorful.

713
01:29:33,576 --> 01:29:35,476
Where are they?

714
01:29:37,947 --> 01:29:39,574
I can't see them.

715
01:29:53,930 --> 01:29:55,557
Let's get outta here!

716
01:31:29,325 --> 01:31:32,385
Tell them to leave the money and go.

717
01:31:33,463 --> 01:31:37,695
Dejen el "dinoro",,, dinero and...

718
01:31:38,334 --> 01:31:40,029
y váyanse,

719
01:31:41,904 --> 01:31:44,600
Que dejemos el dinero y nos vayamos?

720
01:31:45,708 --> 01:31:49,644
Tell them we were hired to take it back.
It's ourjob!

721
01:31:50,113 --> 01:31:52,206
Tell them the money isn't ours.

722
01:31:53,850 --> 01:31:56,876
El dinero,,, no es nuestro,

723
01:31:57,487 --> 01:32:00,888
No, ya no es de ustedes,
Ahora es de nosotros,

724
01:32:01,023 --> 01:32:02,854
Claro!

725
01:32:04,727 --> 01:32:09,824
We'll try telling them again.
It's ourjob. The money isn't ours.

726
01:32:11,567 --> 01:32:14,331
El dinero no es nuestro,

727
01:32:14,537 --> 01:32:18,769
- Lo necesitamos,
- También nosotros lo necesitamos,

728
01:32:20,843 --> 01:32:23,107
- What do you think?
- Not so good.

729
01:32:23,679 --> 01:32:26,113
Can you take the two on the right?

730
01:32:27,116 --> 01:32:32,144
Kid, there's something I think I oughta tell ya.
I never shot anybody before.

731
01:32:35,591 --> 01:32:38,287
One hell of a time to tell me.

732
01:32:38,961 --> 01:32:43,898
Vale más que se hagan a un lado,
porque a lo mejor éstos nos matan,

733
01:32:44,667 --> 01:32:50,469
Try for the two on the right. Aim dead center.
That way if you miss, you still hit something.

734
01:32:50,706 --> 01:32:52,367
- Go!
- Qué?

735
01:32:52,675 --> 01:32:54,905
- Please!
- Qué?

736
01:32:55,211 --> 01:32:57,008
- Por favor,
- Por favor!

737
01:33:46,863 --> 01:33:48,956
Well, we've gone straight.

738
01:33:51,934 --> 01:33:53,595
What'll we try now.

739
01:34:11,087 --> 01:34:14,784
There are other ways of going straight,
you know.

740
01:34:28,604 --> 01:34:31,198
There are other ways of going straight.

741
01:34:34,277 --> 01:34:36,370
There's farming.

742
01:34:38,915 --> 01:34:41,008
We could buy a place.

743
01:34:42,118 --> 01:34:44,211
I don't know how to farm.

744
01:34:48,024 --> 01:34:50,083
What about a ranch, then?

745
01:34:52,395 --> 01:34:57,332
The last time we tried a ranch
was during our rustling days.

746
01:34:57,433 --> 01:35:02,029
And even then we weren't much good at it.
It's hard. Hours are brutal.

747
01:35:03,205 --> 01:35:05,833
No, you gotta be a kid to start a ranch.

748
01:35:20,122 --> 01:35:22,090
Hey.

749
01:35:27,229 --> 01:35:29,527
I might go back ahead of you.

750
01:35:36,539 --> 01:35:38,632
You mean home?

751
01:35:40,309 --> 01:35:42,436
I was thinking of it.

752
01:35:47,717 --> 01:35:49,776
Whatever you want, Etta.

753
01:35:53,990 --> 01:35:56,083
Maybe I'll go.

754
01:36:05,201 --> 01:36:07,294
Hey.

755
01:36:07,970 --> 01:36:11,201
Etta's thinking of maybe
going home ahead of us.

756
01:36:14,977 --> 01:36:17,070
Whatever she wants.

757
01:36:19,348 --> 01:36:21,475
I'll go, then.

758
01:36:58,854 --> 01:37:00,947
Manos arriba!

759
01:37:01,857 --> 01:37:06,317
- How much you got?
- It's hardly worth it. Alpoca Mine.

760
01:37:06,395 --> 01:37:10,331
- I tell you, no more jungle work for me.
- You're getting to be an old maid.

761
01:37:10,399 --> 01:37:13,766
Keep your old-maid remarks to yourself,
if you don't mind.

762
01:37:13,836 --> 01:37:17,636
I'll work in the city and mountains,
but from now on jungle work is out!

763
01:37:18,541 --> 01:37:21,169
Bandidos Yanquis?

764
01:37:21,243 --> 01:37:23,404
Tell them to be quiet.

765
01:37:23,546 --> 01:37:25,946
- What's the word?
- Quietos,

766
01:37:26,015 --> 01:37:28,074
Quietos!

767
01:37:37,626 --> 01:37:40,493
I tell you,
the jungle's a better cover for payrolls.

768
01:37:40,629 --> 01:37:45,293
Kid, I got a right to my opinion, and in
my opinion there are snakes in the jungle.

769
01:37:45,401 --> 01:37:48,097
I don't work around snakes.

770
01:37:48,204 --> 01:37:50,468
What is this place?

771
01:37:50,606 --> 01:37:53,074
I don't know. San Vicente, I think.

772
01:37:53,409 --> 01:37:55,969
- Comer?
- Sí, señor, Pasen,

773
01:37:56,045 --> 01:37:58,513
Juan! Ven, Llévate los caballos,

774
01:38:24,673 --> 01:38:29,474
I don't enjoy jungles or swamps. I don't like
snakes. I don't much care for night work.

775
01:38:29,545 --> 01:38:31,843
Bitch, bitch, bitch.

776
01:38:33,315 --> 01:38:35,875
Capitán! Capitán!

777
01:38:35,951 --> 01:38:39,114
Capitán, allí en la plaza
hay una mula de las minas de Alpoca,

778
01:38:39,221 --> 01:38:41,280
- De las minas de Alpoca?
- Sí, sí,

779
01:38:41,357 --> 01:38:45,726
Allí está, dos hombres la acaban de traer,
están comiendo en el restorán de mi papá,

780
01:38:45,961 --> 01:38:50,125
El guisado está delicioso,
Para chuparse los dedos,

781
01:38:51,133 --> 01:38:54,728
Es la especialidad de la casa,

782
01:38:54,837 --> 01:38:59,865
Se quieren más no tengan pena y díganmelo,
Yo estoy aquí para servirles,

783
01:38:59,942 --> 01:39:03,901
Agradezco la visita
de tan distinguidos caballeros,

784
01:39:03,979 --> 01:39:06,311
Muchas gracias, Para servirles,

785
01:39:06,482 --> 01:39:08,541
- Muchas gracias,
- Sí,

786
01:39:11,954 --> 01:39:15,117
The specialty of the house
and it's still moving!

787
01:39:23,499 --> 01:39:27,458
Well, that settles it.
This place gets no more of my business.

788
01:39:35,211 --> 01:39:36,974
- Hey.
- What?

789
01:39:37,079 --> 01:39:39,206
What do you think?

790
01:39:39,315 --> 01:39:41,374
I bet it's just one guy.

791
01:39:49,325 --> 01:39:51,816
Don't you get sick of being right all the time?

792
01:40:22,258 --> 01:40:24,351
Reloading.

793
01:40:27,029 --> 01:40:29,122
That's all I got.

794
01:40:33,369 --> 01:40:36,964
We're gonna run out unless
we can get to that mule and get some more.

795
01:40:41,377 --> 01:40:43,436
I'll go.

796
01:40:43,545 --> 01:40:46,639
This is no time for bravery. I'll let you.

797
01:40:48,417 --> 01:40:50,282
Loaded.

798
01:40:57,192 --> 01:40:59,820
Hell! I'm the one that has to go.

799
01:41:01,797 --> 01:41:03,287
Why you?

800
01:41:03,399 --> 01:41:06,960
Cos I could never give you cover.
You can cover me.

801
01:41:10,172 --> 01:41:12,640
You can see I'm right, can't you?

802
01:41:18,814 --> 01:41:23,046
- You go.
- Yeah, why am I always so damned smart?

803
01:41:29,858 --> 01:41:31,985
Here. Gimme your gun.

804
01:41:39,101 --> 01:41:41,194
OK. Go!

805
01:41:57,886 --> 01:42:00,047
OK!

806
01:42:38,794 --> 01:42:40,762
Go!

807
01:44:24,833 --> 01:44:27,859
Is... is that what you call giving cover?

808
01:44:28,604 --> 01:44:30,868
Is that what you call running?

809
01:44:31,707 --> 01:44:34,437
If I... knew you were gonna stroll...

810
01:44:35,844 --> 01:44:39,405
You never could shoot,
not from the very beginning.

811
01:44:45,187 --> 01:44:47,280
And you are all mouth!

812
01:44:55,697 --> 01:44:57,790
Jefe, ya llegó el ejército,

813
01:45:09,211 --> 01:45:11,304
Mi capitán!

814
01:45:12,047 --> 01:45:14,311
- Dónde están?
- Allí en la plaza,

815
01:45:14,416 --> 01:45:17,112
- Cuántos hombres son?
- Dos hombres,

816
01:45:17,219 --> 01:45:18,516
- Dos?
- Mi capitán,,,

817
01:45:18,620 --> 01:45:21,214
- Dos?
- Bandidos Yanquis,

818
01:45:22,224 --> 01:45:24,920
- Bandidos Yanquis, eh?
- Sí, mi capitán,

819
01:45:26,328 --> 01:45:30,094
Sargento Rico! Desmonte a veinte hombres
y que vengan con el teniente,

820
01:45:30,165 --> 01:45:33,862
Sargento! Rodeen el zócalo,
y suban hacia la azotea y espérenme,

821
01:45:33,936 --> 01:45:37,497
Media vuelta en el lugar! AI frente!

822
01:46:45,841 --> 01:46:49,333
- I got a great idea where we should go next.
- I don't wanna hear it.

823
01:46:49,444 --> 01:46:52,641
- You'll change your mind when I tell ya.
- Shut up!

824
01:46:52,748 --> 01:46:54,909
- OK, OK.
- Your great ideas got us here...

825
01:46:54,983 --> 01:46:57,850
- Forget it!
- I never wanna hear another of your ideas.

826
01:46:57,953 --> 01:47:00,012
- All right.
- OK.

827
01:47:09,831 --> 01:47:11,924
Australia.

828
01:47:14,236 --> 01:47:18,263
I figured,
secretly you wanted to know, so I told you.

829
01:47:18,373 --> 01:47:20,432
Australia.

830
01:47:21,343 --> 01:47:26,542
- That's your great idea?
- Oh, boy, it's the latest in... in a long line.

831
01:47:26,615 --> 01:47:29,584
- Australia's no better than here.
- That's all you know.

832
01:47:29,651 --> 01:47:32,882
- Name me one thing...
- They speak English in Australia!

833
01:47:32,988 --> 01:47:36,651
- They do?
- Yeah, smart guy. We wouldn't be foreigners.

834
01:47:39,861 --> 01:47:44,560
They got horses in Australia. Hell, they got
thousands of miles we could hide out in.

835
01:47:44,633 --> 01:47:47,067
Good climate, beaches.
You could learn to swim.

836
01:47:47,169 --> 01:47:50,070
No! Swimming isn't important.

837
01:47:52,574 --> 01:47:54,633
What about the banks?

838
01:47:55,377 --> 01:47:58,073
They're easy. Easy, ripe and luscious.

839
01:48:02,784 --> 01:48:04,684
The banks or the women?

840
01:48:04,786 --> 01:48:07,448
Well, once you got one, you got the other!

841
01:48:11,393 --> 01:48:14,920
- It's a long way though.
- Everything's gotta be perfect with you!

842
01:48:15,030 --> 01:48:18,295
I just don't wanna get there
and find out it stinks, that's all.

843
01:48:18,400 --> 01:48:20,459
At least think about it.

844
01:48:22,471 --> 01:48:25,065
All right.

845
01:48:25,140 --> 01:48:27,233
I'll think about it.

846
01:48:31,446 --> 01:48:33,311
Hey.

847
01:48:34,416 --> 01:48:38,079
When we get outside,
when we get to the horses,

848
01:48:38,153 --> 01:48:40,246
just remember one thing.

849
01:48:44,326 --> 01:48:46,658
- Hey, wait a minute.
- What?

850
01:48:47,262 --> 01:48:49,924
You didn't see Lefors out there, did you?

851
01:48:50,031 --> 01:48:52,329
Lefors?

852
01:48:52,434 --> 01:48:54,527
No.

853
01:48:54,669 --> 01:48:56,569
Oh, good.

854
01:48:56,705 --> 01:48:59,833
For a moment there
I thought we were in trouble.

855
01:49:06,882 --> 01:49:09,783
Fuego!

856
01:49:09,885 --> 01:49:12,353
Fuego!

857
01:49:13,955 --> 01:49:16,446
Fuego!
